<resources>
    <string name="app_name">BABY SITTER</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="first_name_prompt">Name:</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="logout">Logout</string>
    <string name="shopping_cart">Shopping Cart</string>
    <string name="about_headline">BABY SITTER HISTORY </string>
    <string name="about_text">BABY SITTER IS AN APP THAT WILL MATCH THE PERFECT BABY SITTER NEAR YOU.
        Henry Twill set out to create supplements and nutritional products
        made from the purest ingredients and backed by scientific and performance data – to
        provide a strong basis of trust and accountability. His quest began while
        training for his first 5K marathon, after recovering from a lengthy injury
        that left him with residual aches, pains, and decreased athletic performance.
        He was disheartened by the vast array of supplements and nutritional products on
        the market that subsisted of lofty claims, and little proof of those claims. He yearned for simple
        and natural ingredients, in their purest form, instead of labels with lengthy chemical names and disclaimers.
        He also cared immensely for the environment, and wanted to find products that were responsibly sourced. When no products
        lived up to his strict requirements, Henry set his sights on creating products that catered to his own vision. Today tha
        t vision has become H+ Sport…offering a variety of supplements, energy bars, rehydration solutions, and active wear that
        complement active lifestyles. At the foundation of H+ Sports are products backed by scientific and performance data,
        that have been created using natural and renewable resources. H+ Sport is dedicated to creating eco-friendly, high-quality,
        nutrient-rich, nutritional products that enhance active lifestyles. In addition, our H+ Sport Active clothing line is made t
        o be functional, stylish, comfortable, and durable, using all natural and organic fibers.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_about">About BABY SITTER</string>
    <string name="title_activity_detail">Detail Activity</string>
    <string name="iam_babysitter">Apply to be a babysitter</string>
    <string name="iam_babymama">Find your babysitter</string>

    <!-- Strings related to login -->
    <string name="prompt_email">Email</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Password (optional)</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in">Sign in or register</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">Sign in</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_email">This email address is invalid</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_password">This password is too short</string>
    <string name="error_incorrect_password">This password is incorrect</string>
    <string name="error_field_required">This field is required</string>
    <string name="permission_rationale">"Contacts permissions are needed for providing email
        completions."
    </string>

    <string name="login_button">Dummy Button</string>
    <string name="dummy_content">DUMMY\nCONTENT</string>
    <string name="large_text">DUMMY\nCONTENT</string>

    <string name="hint_email">Email</string>
    <string name="hint_password">Password</string>
    <string name="hint_first_name">First Name</string>
    <string name="hint_last_name">Last Name</string>

    <string name="btn_login">LOGIN</string>
    <string name="btn_register">REGISTER</string>
    <string name="btn_link_to_register">Not a member? Sign up now.</string>
    <string name="btn_link_to_login">Already registred! Login Me.</string>
    <string name="welcome">Welcome</string>
    <string name="btn_logout">LOGOUT</string>
    <string name="name">Fullname</string>
    <string name="hint_address"> Address (2025 E.st, San Francisco, CA, 94115)</string>
    <string name="hint_phone">Phone Number</string>


    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

</resources>
